http://www.oxygenxml.com/privacy_policy.html

Toggle navigationXML EditorProductsShopResourcesSupportCompany
Editing & DevelopingOxygen XML EditorThe Premier All-In-One XML Editing SuiteOxygen XML DeveloperAll the Tools You Need for Designing XML Schemas and Transformation
PipelinesOxygen XML AuthorSingle-Source XML Authoring and Multi-Channel PublishingPublishingOxygen Publishing EngineThe Complete DITA Publishing Solution for WebHelp and PDF OutputOxygen XML WebHelpPublish DITA and DocBook Content to WebHelp OutputOxygen PDF ChemistryChemistry Converts HTML and XML to PDF Using CSSOxygen FeedbackModern Commenting Platform CloudEnterpriseCollaboration & ReviewOxygen XML Web AuthorEngage Your Whole Organization In Content CreationOxygen Content FusionWeb Collaboration Solution for any XML Documentation Review
WorkflowExtensibility and AutomationOxygen SDKOxygen XML ScriptingShopPricing and licesing for businesses, Academic and individuals Sales
FAQ Register
Code Sales
Support
Resellers
Documentation
Videos Blog
Download Oxygen
SDK License ServerSpell CheckingRelease HistoryOther ResourcesLogo ResourcesPromotional Items Sales Support Technical Support ForumMailing ListsContact UsTestimonials
Partners Events News Case
StudiesAbout UsCustomersQuotesCareersLegalPrivacy Policy(last updated June 2019)This Privacy Policy sets out how Syncro Soft SRL ("Syncro","we") collects, uses and
protects Your Personal Data (as defined below) that you provide when you visit our websites
("Sites") and when you use our software products ("Products") and services
("Services").Personal data ("Personal Data") means any information related to an identified or
identifiable person. An identifiable person is a person who can be identified, directly or
indirectly, in particular by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors
specific to the person.Syncro Soft SRL is a Romanian company registered under the number RO10639959. Our head
office address is Remus 5A, Craiova, 200082, Romania with a general office phone number of
+40251461480.Information We Collect From YouSyncro collects your Personal Data in various ways, such as via email, over the
internet when you register on our Sites, fill out a form, post on our forum, request
support using the available official channels, or when you activate or purchase Products
and Services. We may also collect Personal Data about you from third parties, including
(but not limited to) from our partners, agents and resellers. The Personal Data you
provide us may include: first and last name, company name, email address, phone number,
mailing address, and any other identifier that permits us to contact you.We collect Personal Data from you at several different instances, including but not
limited to the following: when you use or visit our Sites, some information is automatically collected,
such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your operating system, the browser type,
the address of a referring web site, and your activity on our Sites. If you access the
Sites from a mobile device, we may also collect information about the type of mobile
device you use, your device’s unique ID, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use.
when you purchase a Product or access to a Service. We do this to be able to
deliver our Products and Services, to process financial transactions, to send you
important product and services announcements, operational information, and for legal
reasons. Please note that our website's financial transactions and data pertaining to
those transactions are handled through 2Checkout or
ShareIt.
when you activate a Product or Service, we may collect information that
identifies you in accordance with our licensing model. This information is compared
against our license information for authentication. During the activation process,
information about the following may be sent to Syncro via an internet connection or by
email: IP, MAC address, and the version of Product in use on your computer.
when you request a free trial or register as an end-user for our Products or
Services.
when we correspond with you as a customer or prospective customer, or when you
contact us for help or information.
when you submit a product or service support request (including product crash
report dialogues, error reports, improvement requests, or analytics data).
when you subscribe to email communications, user community forums, blogs, and
newsletters. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose any information through
our public mailing list, blogs, or forums, this information may be collected and used by
others, for which Syncro shall not have any responsibility.
when you register for training, webinars, conferences, events, or other
exclusive content.
when we meet you at events (conferences, meet-ups) and you provide us with your
contact details in order for us to contact you about our Products and Services.
when you post business or personal testimonials and other endorsements as a
satisfied customer on our Sites.
when you contact us for a career enquiry (job application), we collect personal
information in connection with administration of our human resources programs and
functions. Vendors That Collect Anonymous Data on Our Behalf: We use Google Analytics to analyse the performance of our
websites and follow up on the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. Google Analytics
allow us to analyse data in aggregate, we do not collect or store any personal
information in Google Analytics. If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics
monitoring your behaviour on our sites, please use this link (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).
We use YouTube to store videos that we show on our website.
YouTube uses a cookie to collect anonymous viewing information that we use to find out
how videos are being viewed.
We occasionally use a variety of new technologies and social media options to
communicate and interact with customers, potential customers, employees, and potential
employees. These sites and applications include popular social networking and media
sites, open source software communities, and more. To better engage with the public in
ongoing dialog, we use certain third-party platforms including, but not limited to,
Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn. These third-party websites and applications are
web-based technologies that are not exclusively operated or controlled by us. When
interacting on those websites, you may reveal certain personal information to us or to
third parties. Other than when used by our employees for the purpose of responding to
a specific message or request, we will not use, share, or retain your personal
information.
You can log into some of our Services using sign-in services such as
GitHub/Google OAuth, or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your
identity and provide you with the option to share with us certain personal
information, such as your name and email address, to pre-populate our sign-up form.
How We Use the InformationSyncro’s legal basis for using your Personal Data will depend on the type of personal
information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. Below are the
specific purposes for which we use the information we collect about you: to process and complete transactions, and send related information, including
transaction confirmations and invoices. We send transactional communications via email,
either directly or through one of our resellers, and/or within the Products and
Services, including confirming your purchases, reminding you of subscription and trial
expirations.
to contact customers with technical alerts, updates, upgrades and enhancements,
security notifications, as well as administrative communications.
to provide customer support. We use your information to resolve technical issues
you encounter, to respond to your requests for assistance, to analyze crash information,
to verify your identity as a customer, and to fix and improve the Products and Services,
according to our Technical Support
Policy.
to send you informational or promotional content about new products and
services, events, webinars, special offers or other information which we think you may
find interesting. However, you can always unsubscribe or choose not to receive
promotional information from us by following the specific instructions in the email you
receive or by notifying us via the appropriate method below.
to send you communications as you on-board to a particular Product or Service to
help you become more proficient in using that Product or Service. These communications
are part of the Product or Service Notifications Feed and you can opt-out of them (you
will find that option within the communication itself or in your Product/Service Global
Settings).
for other purposes made clear to you at the time you submit your information
(for example, to fulfill your request for a demo, to provide you with access to one of
our webinars or whitepapers or to provide you with information you have requested about
our products and services).
to follow up with you after you meet us at a trade show or industry event, and
you leave your contact details for us.
to review your skills and experience for employment, if you apply for a job
application within Syncro.
for legitimate business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud
monitoring and prevention, developing new products, improving or modifying our Products
and Services, and identifying usage trends.
to comply with applicable laws, comply with legal and regulatory processes,
enforce our terms and conditions, and protect our operations, rights, safety, or
property. Note:If you do not wish to provide us with your Personal Data, and processing such
data is necessary for the performance of a contract with you and to fulfil our
contractual obligations to you, we may not be able to perform our obligations under the
contract between us.How and Why We Use CookiesSyncro Soft websites use "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to
help personalize your online experience. We also use traffic log cookies to identify which
web pages are being access. This helps us analyse data about web pages traffic and improve
our websites in order to tailor them to customer needs. Overall, cookies help us provide
you with better websites, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which
you do not. Please read more about the cookies we use in our Cookies Policy. A cookie in no way gives us
access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to
share with us.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically
accept cookies, but you can modify your browser settings to decline cookies, if you
prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other
interactive features of Syncro Soft websites and web services that depend on
cookies.How We Share Your InformationWe take care to allow your Personal Data to be accessed only by those who really need
to in order to perform their tasks and duties, and to share with third parties who have a
legitimate purpose for accessing it. We may share Personal Data about you with third
parties in the following circumstances:Service Providers: We may share your information with third parties,
such as vendors, consultants, agents and other service providers who work on our behalf.
Examples include vendors and service providers who provide assistance with billing,
processing credit card payments, hosting, storage, technical support, and customer
service. If a service provider needs to access information about you to perform services
on our behalf, they do so under close instruction from us, including policies and
procedures designed to protect your information. If you have registered for a
Syncro event, we may share your personal information with the event venue or industry
partners to help with the logistics on the day. We will clearly state the venue and
partner on the event landing page.Business Partners : From time to time, we may engage in joint sales or
product promotions with selected business partners. If you purchase or specifically
express interest in a jointly-offered product, promotion, or service, we may share
relevant personal information with those partners. Please be aware that Syncro does not
control our business partners’ use of such information. Our partners are responsible for
managing their own use of the personal information collected in these circumstances. We
recommend you review the privacy policies of the relevant partner to find out more about
their handling of your personal information. Compliance with laws or any competent law enforcement body, regulatory body,
government agency, court or third party: We may disclose personal
information, or any information you submitted via our software products if we have a
good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary
to: (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental
request; (ii) enforce our policies, including investigations of potential violations
thereof; (iii) investigate, detect, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities
or other wrongdoing, suspected fraud, or security issues; (iv) to establish or exercise
our rights to defend against legal claims; (v) prevent harm to the rights, property, or
safety of us, our users, yourself, or any third party; or (vi) for the purpose of
collaborating with law enforcement agencies or in case we find it necessary in order to
enforce intellectual property or other legal rights. Business transfers: We may share or transfer your information in
connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets,
financing, acquisition, dissolution, corporate reorganization, or similar event. We will
inform any buyer that your information shall only be used in accordance with this
Privacy Policy. With your consent: We may disclose your Personal Data for any purpose
with your consent. Other legitimate business purposes: We may share your Personal Data
when it is necessary for other legitimate purposes such as protecting Syncro's
confidential and proprietary information or where necessary to support, respond to and
to provide our products and services to our customers. Note:We do not share, sell, rent, or trade any of
your Personal Data with third parties for their own promotional
purposes.Your Privacy RightsIndividuals located in certain countries, including the European Economic Area
(“EEA”), have certain statutory rights in relation to their Personal Data. Below are the
rights that you have under law, and what Syncro does to protect those rights:The right to be informed. Syncro is publishing this Privacy Policy to
keep you informed as to what we do with your personal information. We strive to be
transparent about how we use your data. The right to access. You may have the right to access the personal
information that we hold about you. When you exercise your right to request access to
the information Syncro processes about you, you will not have to pay a fee to access
your personal data. However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly
unfounded, repetitive, or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your
request in these circumstances. The right to rectification. If the information Syncro holds about you
is inaccurate or not complete, you may have the right to ask us to rectify it. If that
data has been passed to a third party with your consent or for legal reasons, then we
will ask them to rectify the data. The right to erasure. This is sometimes called ‘the right to be
forgotten’. In certain circumstances, you may have the right to the erasure of
personal information that we hold about you (for example if it is no longer necessary
for the purposes for which it was originally collected). Please note, however, that we
may need to retain certain information for record keeping purposes, to complete
transactions, or to comply with our legal obligations. The right to restrict processing. You may have the right to request
that we restrict processing of your personal information in certain circumstances (for
example, where you believe that the personal information we hold about you is not
accurate or lawfully held). This means we are permitted to store the data but not
further process it. We keep just enough data to make sure we respect your request in the
future. The right to portability. You may have the right to be provided with
your personal data in a structured, machine readable and commonly used format, and to
request that we transfer the personal information provided by you to another service or
provider. The right to object. You may have the right to object to our processing
of your personal data for purposes based on our legitimate interests. In some cases, we
may be able to demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your
information which overrides your rights and freedoms. The right to withdraw consent. We may seek to rely on your consent in
order to process certain personal information. Where we do so, you have the right not to
provide your consent or to withdraw your consent at any time. You can opt-out of
receiving marketing communications from Syncro by clicking "unsubscribe" in any
marketing email communications we send you, or by sending an email to . Please note that if we
can also rely on other bases to process your personal data aside from consent, then we
may do so even if you have withdrawn your consent. The right to comply to Supervisory Authority. You have the right to
complain to the Supervisory Authority if you feel that Syncro has not responded to your
requests to solve a problem. The right in relation to automated decision making and profiling. If we
use either automated decision making or profiling, then you have a right to know. Also,
we need your consent if either of these are used to make a decision that affects you. As
with all consent, you can withdraw it at any time. If you would like to exercise any of the above rights, please contact
so that we may consider your
request under applicable law (see Privacy Complaints section).How Long We Keep InformationWe will retain Personal Data we collect from you where we have a justifiable business
need to do so and/or for as long as is needed to fulfill the purposes outlined in this
Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as
tax, legal, accounting, or other purposes). After such time, we will either delete or
anonymize your information or, if this is not possible (for example, because the
information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your
information and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible. How long we
keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information, as described in
further detail below:
If you are a customer, partner, or prospect, we keep the information for the
duration of our relationship. Due to the possibility of long sales cycles, one never
knows when a potential client will re-engage with Syncro and having the background and
history of the contracting party will assist Syncro in providing a better service.
Therefore, please note that unless you instruct us otherwise, we retain the information
we collect for as long as needed to provide our Products and Services and to comply with
our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
When you contact us for technical support, we may keep a record of your
communication to help solve any issues that you might be facing. Your information may be
retained for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including
for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirement.
If you have requested to receive marketing communications, we will keep your
personal information only for as long as you interact with us, or until the data subject
opts-out or asks to be forgotten. You can request deletion of your Personal Data at any time (see "Your Privacy Rights"
section for further information) and we will consider your request in accordance with
applicable laws.Transfer of Personal DataWe may store data on remote servers operated by a cloud service provider to Syncro
rather than storing it on our own servers. Regardless of where you use our online services
or provide information to us, the information may be transferred to and maintained on
servers located outside the country in which the data was collected (or, in the case of
personal data collected within the European Economic Area (“EEA”), to countries outside
the EEA). By providing any data through the online services, you hereby expressly consent
to such transferring and processing of your data in such third countries.Use By MinorsThe Sites, the Products, and the Services are not intended for use by minors. Syncro
does not knowingly collect any personal data from persons under the age of 18 and will
immediately delete any such data subsequently so determined. If you believe that we have
mistakenly or unintentionally collected a minor’s personal information, please contact us
at .Links to Third Party WebsitesSyncro websites may contain links to other websites, which are outside our control and
are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other websites using the links
provided, the operators of these websites may collect information about you that will be
used in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. We encourage you
to ask questions before you disclose any personal information to others.'Do Not Track' Signals under the California Online Protection Act (CalOPPA) Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy setting in your web browsers that enables you to
opt out of tracking by websites and online services. When you activate DNT, the browser
will send a message requesting that the website or online service not track you.
Currently, our website does not recognize DNT signals. Instead, information collection and
sharing practices, as well as the choices we provide you, will continue to operate as
described in this Privacy Policy, regardless of whether a DNT signal is received. Data SecurityWe use reasonable measures to safeguard personally identifiable information, which
measures are appropriate to the type of information maintained, and follows applicable
laws regarding the safeguarding of any such information under our control.Syncro trains all staff who handle Personal Data on the importance of and procedure
for maintaining confidentiality. All employees, contractors, consultants, and service
providers of Syncro who are provided access to such information on behalf of Syncro are
required to be familiar with and comply with the provisions of this Privacy Policy and
applicable laws.Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be
guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, despite our efforts, we cannot guarantee its
absolute security. The Internet by its nature is a public forum, and we encourage you to
use caution when disclosing information online. We do not warrant or represent that
personal information about you will be protected against loss, misuse, or alteration by
third parties.Privacy ComplaintsSyncro Soft takes its users' privacy concerns very seriously. If you believe that
Syncro Soft has not complied with this Privacy Policy in respect to your personal
information, you may write an email to the Syncro Soft Privacy Officer at the following
address: . In your email
or letter, please describe in as much detail as possible, the ways in which you believe
that the Privacy Policy has not been followed. We will investigate your complaint
promptly. We will respond to written requests within thirty (30) days of receiving such request.
We will either make the requested information available within that time period, or
provide written notice of an extension where additional time is required to fulfill the
request. If Syncro cannot fulfill your request in full or in part, you will be provided
with a response in writing that documents the reason(s) for refusal and the recourse
available to you.Privacy Policy ChangesThis Privacy Policy was last changed on May 22, 2018. Syncro may change this policy by
updating this page and reserves the right to do so without notification. However, if any
significant or material changes are made, a notice will clearly be provided to you when
you next visit the site so you can choose to review it before proceeding. We encourage you
to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy
practices.If you have any questions regarding your personal data and how we may use it,
including any queries relating to this Policy, please contact us at
(with the subject heading
“Data Protection”).Oxygen XML EditorStarting from Academic $99Personal $198Business $688Buy NowDownloadVideo TutorialsPDF BrochureTechnical SupportUser ManualUpcoming Events
Custom Business Rules for DITA Projects
- presented by Octavian NadoluWed, December 16, 2020ProductsXML EditorXML DeveloperXML AuthorXML Web AuthorContent FusionPublishing EngineWebHelpPDF ChemistryFeedbackFeaturesWYSIWYG EditorsSchema EditorWSDL EditorXSLT
EditorXQueryXSD DocumentationXML DatabasesSVN ClientEPUB EditorDITA EditorDocBook EditorShopBuy NowSales FAQResellersResourcesDocumentationVideosOxygen SDKsSpell CheckingSupportSupportForumMailing
ListsContact UsCompanyAbout UsEvents ProgrammePartnersCase StudiesQuotesPress RoomCareersLegalOxygen XML on FacebookFollow Oxygen XML on TwitterOxygen XML Web FeedOxygen XML BlogOxygen XML Youtube Channel © 2002-2020 SyncRO Soft SRL. All rights reserved.
Sitemap | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
This website was created & generated with
<oXygen/>®XML EditorOur website uses cookies. Find out more about cookies.I understand. Hide this message.
